Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
My name
is Grey Worm.
I come from
the Summer "Ills."
Isles.
Summer Isles.
I am from an island
called Naath.
When they took you?
"When did they take me?"
I was five years old.
You remember your home?
I remember when they
rowed us away from shore.
How white the beaches were.
How tall the trees.
And I remember
my village burning.
Smoke rising into the sky.
Do you remember your home?
Unsullied.
Always Unsullied.
Before Unsullied. nothing.
That's not true.
Perhaps one day you will
return to the Summer Isles.
I don't want return.
Kill the masters.
How are the lessons coming?
Very well. Your Grace.
Missandei is teacher
good. my queen.
You'll have to continue later.
It's time.
_
Mhysa! Mhysa! Mhysa!
Mhysa! Mhysa!
Remind me. Ser Jorah.
how many children did the Great
Masters nail to mileposts?
163. Khaleesi.
Yes. that was it.
Your Grace.
may I have a word?
The city is yours.
All these people.
they're your subjects now.
Sometimes it is better
to answer injustice
with mercy.
I will answer injustice
with justice.
What the hell was that?
That was me knocking
your ass to the dirt
with your own hand.
You're a rare talent.
When you're fighting
cripples. anyway.
You learned to fight
like a good little boy.
I'll bet that thrust through the Mad
King's back was pretty as a picture.
You want to fight pretty
or you want to win?
You talk to my brother this way?
All the time.
He got used to it.
Do you think he did it?
No.
Oh. he hated
the little twat. sure.
But who didn't?
And poison's not his style.
Or murder. for that matter.
You want to know for sure.
why don't you ask him?
You haven't been
to see him yet. eh?
We're done for today.
Your brother ever tell you
how I came into his service?
You stood for him in his trial
by combat at the Eyrie.
Aye.
But only when
Lady Arryn demanded
the trial take place that day.
You were his first choice.
He named you for his champion
because he knew you would ride day
and night to come fight for him.
You gonna fight for him now?
To tell you the truth.
this isn't so bad.
Four walls.
A pot to piss in.
I was chained to a wooden post
covered in my own
shit for months.
Is that supposed
to make me feel better?
Maybe a bit.
I'm sorry I didn't come sooner.
It's complicated. yes.
- So how is our sister?
- How do you think?
Her son died in her arms.
Her son?
Don't.
You know what's coming?
My trial for regicide.
Yes. I know.
I know the whole bloody
country thinks I'm guilty.
I know that one
of my three judges
has wished me dead more
times than I can count.
And that judge is my father.
As for Cersei.
well. she's probably
working on a way
to avoid a trial altogether
by having me killed.
Now that you mention it.
she did ask.
So. should I turn around
and close my eyes?
Depends.
Did you do it?
The Kingslayer brothers.
You like it?
I like it.
You're really asking
if I killed your son?
Are you really asking
if I'd kill my brother?
How can I help you?
Well. you could set me free.
You know I can't.
Then there's really
nothing else to say.
What do you want me to do?
Kill the guards?
Sneak you out of the city
in the back of a cart?
I'm the Lord Commander
of the Kingsguard.
Sorry. I'd forgotten.
I'd hate for you to do
something inappropriate.
Inappropriate?
You're accused of killing the king.
Freeing you is treason.
Except I didn't do it.
Which is why
we're having a trial.
A trial.
If the killer threw himself
before the Iron Throne.
confessed to his crimes. and gave
irrefutable evidence of his guilt.
it wouldn't matter to Cersei.
She won't rest
until my head's on a spike.
Not just yours.
She's offering a knighthood
to whomever finds Sansa Stark.
Sansa couldn't have done this.
She had more reason than
anyone in the Seven Kingdoms.
Do you think it's a coincidence she
disappeared the same night Joffrey died?
No. but...
Sansa's not a killer.
Not yet. anyway.
Where are you taking me?
I'm getting married
to your Aunt Lysa.
She's waiting for us
at the Eyrie.
You'll be safe there.
Did you kill Joffrey?
Did I kill Joffrey?
I've been in the Vale for weeks.
I know it was you.
And who helped me
with this conspiracy?
Well. there was Ser Dontos.
You used him to get
me out of King's Landing.
but you would never trust
him to kill the king.
- Why not? - Because you're too smart
to trust a drunk.
Then perhaps it was
your husband.
No.
How do you know?
I just do.
You're right.
He wasn't involved
in Joffrey's death.
But you were.
Do you remember that lovely
necklace Dontos gave you?
I don't suppose you noticed
that a stone was missing
after the feast.
The poison.
I don't understand.
The Lannisters gave you
wealth. power.
Joffrey made you
the Lord of Harrenhal.
A man with no motive
is a man no one suspects.
Always keep your foes confused.
If they don't know who
you are or what you want.
they can't know
what you plan to do next.
I don't believe you.
If they catch you. they'll
put your head on a spike
just like my father's.
You'd risk that
just to confuse them?
So many men.
they risk so little.
They spend their lives
avoiding danger.
And then they die.
I'd risk everything
to get what I want.
And what do you want?
Everything.
My friendship with the
Lannisters was productive.
But Joffrey.
a vicious boy with
a crown on his head.
is not a reliable ally.
And who could trust
a friend like that?
Who could trust you?
I don't want friends like me.
My new friends are predictable.
Very reasonable people.
As for what happened to Joffrey.
well. that was something my new
friends wanted very badly.
Nothing like a thoughtful gift
to make a new friendship
grow strong.
I can't believe you're going.
Leaving me alone here
with these people.
The time has come. my dear.
There's nothing
more tedious than a trial.
Except perhaps these gardens.
If I have to take one
more leisurely stroll
through these gardens. I'll
fling myself from the cliffs.
Have you been to see Tommen yet?
No.
Have they even agreed
to the match?
No one tells me anything.
I wasn't originally meant to marry
your grandfather Luthor. you know.
He was engaged to my sister.
your great-aunt Viola.
I was to be given to
some Targaryen or other.
Marrying a Targaryen
was all the rage back then.
But the moment
I saw my intended.
with his twitchy
little ferret's face
and ludicrous silver hair.
I knew he wouldn't do.
So the evening
before Luthor was
to propose to my sister.
I got lost on my way back
from my embroidery lesson
and happened upon his chamber.
- How absentminded of me.
- Mm-hmm.
The following morning. Luthor
never made it down the stairs
to propose to my sister 'cause
the boy couldn't bloody walk.
And once he could.
the only thing he wanted
was what I'd given him
the night before.
I was good.
I was very. very good.
You are even better.
But you need to act quickly.
Cersei may be vicious.
but she's not stupid.
She'll turn the boy against
you as soon as she can.
And by the time you're
married. it'll be too late.
Luckily for you.
the Queen Regent
is rather distracted
at the moment.
mourning her dear departed boy.
Accusing her brother
of his murder.
which he didn't commit.
Well. he could have done.
He could have done.
but he didn't.
- You don't know. Grandmother.
- But I do know.
You don't think I'd let you
marry that beast. do you?
What?
I don't understand.
Shh. Don't you worry
yourself about all that.
You just do
what needs to be done.
Bring it through!
And again.
Very nice. Good.
A lot of wildlings fight
with a weapon in each hand.
First thing you want to do
is disarm them to try
and even the odds.
Let's see what you can do.
Olly. you just watch for now.
I can fight.
Have you ever
held a sword before?
I was the best archer
in our hamlet.
I was!
I believe you.
We'll go hunting
for rabbits one day.
Right now. watch and learn.
You two.
Take it slow.
try and disarm each other.
You know how to fight.
You could have gone
easier on him.
He wouldn't have learned
anything that way.
Lord Snow.
What do you think you're doing?
Grenn and I were helping them.
Grenn's a ranger.
You're a steward.
Maybe you forgot that while you
were off with your wildling bitch.
but I didn't.
Someone has to train them.
And that someone isn't you.
Go find a chamber pot to empty.
Go on. Do it.
You traitor's bastard.
Give me an excuse.
Mormont's not here
to protect you now.
Get back to work.
Now!
I said now!
The bastard's well-liked.
You're not.
You think I care if they like me?
We're at war.
For now.
But you can't be
acting commander forever.
There will be a choosing.
The old maester
will insist on it.
You might reconsider
his request to march
on Craster's.
Let the mutineers
take care of Snow.
Or you might be taking
orders from him
the rest of your life.
A bastard. eh?
Took you for highborn.
My father was highborn.
My mother wasn't.
Name's Locke.
Jon Snow.
You fight well.
What brought you up here?
A sense of duty.
I wanted to do my part
for the safety of the realm.
I was a game warden
in the Stormlands.
Fed a prized partridge
to my hungry kids.
I was stupid enough
to get caught.
Chose the Wall
over losing my hand.
Figured I wouldn't have to suck
up to any highborn cunts here.
Come on. get on with it.
What are you
waiting for? Summer?
Guess I was wrong.
You sent for me. Your Grace?
Your Grace.
How formal of you.
How many Kingsguards are
posted outside Tommen's door?
Ser Boros is on duty tonight.
- Tomorrow I believe--
-  So one?
You have one man
guarding the future king?
I promise you Tommen's safe.
We're protecting him.
The way you protected Joffrey?
Why did Catelyn Stark
set you free?
- What?
- I've been wondering for months.
Ever since that great cow brought
you back to the capital.
Why did she set you free?
You know why. She'd hoped I'd
send her daughters back to her.
She hoped or did you promise?
I swore by all the gods
that if her daughters were
alive. I'd return them to her.
So you made a sacred vow
to the enemy.
I wanted to get back to you.
Should I have told her
to fuck off?
You didn't mean it. then?
You have no loyalty
to Catelyn Stark?
Catelyn Stark's dead.
So if I told you to leave the
capital right now and find Sansa.
if I told you to find that
murderous little bitch
and bring me her head.
would you do it?
I know you went to see Tyrion.
That creature
who murdered our son.
I had to see him.
I had to know for myself.
And?
He didn't do it. Cersei.
You've always pitied him.
Our poor little brother.
Abused by the world.
Despised by his father
and sister.
He'd kill us all if he could.
I want four men at Tommen's
door day and night.
That will be all.
Lord Commander.
Ser Pounce?
How did you get past
the Kingsguard?
Kingsguard.
I don't think you're
supposed to be here.
Mother doesn't allow me
to have visitors at night.
I'm not a visitor. Your Grace.
Word has it
I'm to be your bride.
Did you know that people
in arranged marriages
often never meet
until their wedding day?
Before we decide to spend
our lives together.
we ought to get
to know one another.
Don't you think?
Yes.
But if my mother
found out--
It can be our secret.
Hmm?
If we're going to be
man and wife.
we'll have a few secrets
from her. I hope.
So. Your Grace...
Yes?
Tell me a secret.
Hello. Aren't you
a proper fellow?
That's Ser Pounce.
Very handsome.
Joffrey didn't like him.
He threatened to skin him alive
and mix his innards
up in my food
so I wouldn't know
I was eating him.
That's very cruel.
You don't strike me as cruel.
No.
I don't think I am.
That's a relief.
Because you know
what happens when we marry?
We say our vows in front
of the high septon.
And after the ceremony.
there's a feast.
When we marry. I become yours.
Forever.
It's getting late.
I should go.
May I come and visit you again?
All right. then.
Remember.
our little secret.
"Ser Jaime Lannister.
Knighted and named to the
Kingsguard in his 16th year.
At the sack of King's Landing.
murdered his king Aerys II.
Pardoned by Robert Baratheon.
Thereafter known
as the Kingslayer."
It's the duty of the Lord
Commander to fill those pages.
And there's still room
left on mine.
Valyrian steel.
Mmm.
It's yours.
I can't accept this.
It was reforged
from Ned Stark's sword.
You'll use it to defend
Ned Stark's daughter.
You swore an oath to return the
Stark girls to their mother.
Lady Stark's dead.
Arya's probably dead. too.
but there's still a chance to find
Sansa and get her somewhere safe.
I've got something else for you.
I hope I got
your measurements right.
I'll find her.
For Lady Catelyn.
And for you.
I almost forgot.
I have one more gift.
I don't need a squire.
Of course you do.
He'll slow me down.
My brother owes him a debt.
He's not safe here.
You're keeping him from harm.
It's chivalry.
I won't
slow you down. ser--
my lady.
I promise I'll serve you well.
See? He's a good lad.
You'll get along.
Compliments of Lord Tyrion.
His axe from the Blackwater.
What are you
waiting for. a kiss?
Ready the lady's horse.
They say the best swords
have names.
Any ideas?
Oathkeeper.
Good-bye. Brienne.
Come on. move.
I should never
have taken her away.
- She wasn't safe here.
- She's not safe out there.
I should have known.
You told us there were
wildlings south of the Wall.
If they're raiding the smaller
villages. Mole's Town could be next.
- Castle Black could be next.
- I should go back for Gilly.
We have orders. No one's
to leave the castle.
I remember when you disobeyed
orders and rode south to help Robb.
And I remember who came after
me and brought me home.
I know how hard
it is. Sam. believe me.
When you told me about Bran
going beyond the Wall.
all I could think about was getting my
strength back so I could go and find him.
I wish I could have convinced
him to come back with me.
I tried.
Really. I did.
How fast could they travel?
A crippled boy being pulled
on a sledge by a simpleton?
I don't know.
They'd pass wildling villages.
They could try to find
shelter at one of them.
The wildlings
have joined up with Mance.
Every village or sheltered
place will be deserted.
Except...
Craster's?
You think Bran
might have found--
Snow.
I don't mean to interrupt.
Thorne wants to see you.
Your foray to Craster's Keep.
I'll sanction it.
But I won't order
anyone to go with you.
Volunteers only.
Thank you. Ser Alliser.
Ahem. brothers.
I'm going beyond the Wall
to Craster's Keep.
I'm going to capture the mutineers
holed up there or kill them.
I'm asking for volunteers
to come with me.
There's 60 miles of wilderness
between here and Craster's
and Mance Rayder has an army
bearing down on us.
but we have to do this.
Our survival may depend on
us getting to these mutineers
before Mance does.
They know the Wall.
They know our defenses.
If Mance learns what
they know. we're lost.
But if that's not enough.
then consider this.
If the Night's Watch
are truly brothers.
then Lord Commander Mormont
was our father.
He lived and died for the Watch
and he was betrayed
by his own men.
Stabbed in the back by cowards.
He deserved far better.
All we can give him now
is justice.
Who will join me?
I can't let a recruit
come north of the Wall.
Then let me say my vows.
If it's a fight you're heading for.
then you need men who know how.
Thank you. brothers.
No. don't.
Don't. please.
Please don't. Ow!
You're hurting me.
Karl Tanner from Gin Alley
drinking wine from the skull
of Jeor fucking Mormont.
Any command for us.
Lord Commander?
What's that?
Fuck 'em till they're dead?
Did you hear that. boys?
Fuck 'em till they're dead.
Rast.
Go outside and feed the beast.
We should kill that thing.
You should shut
your fucking hole.
ugly little cunt.
You look like
a fucking ballsack.
Ugly. Look at your
stupid cunt face.
I could piss in any gutter
and soak five of you.
Know how much they paid me to
kill a man in King's Landing?
Seven silvers.
They told me a man's name and that
man never saw daylight again.
None of them cocksuckers
got away from me.
Haven't lost a fight
since I was nine.
Maybe it's time.
What do you think. eh?
Maybe you're the man.
Eh. cunt?
I wouldn't stand a chance.
None of us would.
I was a fucking legend
in Gin Alley.
A fucking legend!
I would take any knight--
any knight. any time.
Fucking cunts in steel plate.
Fucking cowards.
- A gift for the gods.
A gift for the gods.
What the fuck is that?
Craster's last child.
A boy.
What am I supposed
to do with him?
What did Craster do with 'em?
Kill 'em before they could grow
up and do the same to him?
All right.
Don't need another
mouth to feed.
- Hand him over.
- He didn't kill them.
- He offered them.
- To who?
To the gods.
The white walkers.
A gift for the gods.
Shut up!
So...
if it worked for him...
Let's give the walkers
what they want.
Rast is headed that way.
Pink-eyed fuck.
You thirsty?
Fuck!
Hodor.
Do you hear that?
Is that a baby?
It's coming.
I'm going out there.
No. we need to stay together.
I'm going.
- Bran. Bran.
- Hodor. Hodor.
- Hodor.
- Bran. what happened?
Summer. he's hurt. They've
caught him in a trap.
Who?
I didn't see. but they
have my brother's wolf.
They have Ghost.
They're Night's Watch.
Look.
Jon might be here.
If Jon was here. why would
they put his wolf in a cage?
They might have been Night's
Watch once. not anymore.
We're not safe here.
We need to go.
No.
Bran. we need to go now.
I'm not leaving without Summer.
Can you remember
where the cage was?
The east side of the keep.
If I'm not back
soon. we'll meet--
Hodor.
If I was your size. I'd be
king of the fucking world.
Help him up.
This is nice.
Fine leather.
You're no wildling.
Important. Highborn.
Who are you?
You see. where I come from.
a commoner like me slaps
a little lord like you.
I'd lose my right hand.
But we're a long way
from home. aren't we?
And the two of you.
fancy-looking folks
north of the Wall
creeping through the woods.
Isn't that a bit odd?
I like your curly hair.
My mom had curls like that.
Beautiful brown curls.
Why'd you drag a crippled
boy all the way up here?
See you haven't played
this game before.
A highborn hostage.
that's valuable.
But three of them.
that's a lot of mouths to feed.
- What the fuck's wrong with him?
- Come here.
No. please.
Please.
Please. let me help him.
- Who are you?
- Please.
- I'm Brandon Stark!
I'm Brandon Stark of Winterfell.
It's Jon Snow's brother.
It's Meera. It's Meera.
I'm right here.
And I thought this was gonna
be another boring day.
I'm right here.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm